{
  "user": [
    {
      "id": 0,
      "email": "Chandler@abc",
      "password": "Bing",
      "type": "admin",
      "firstName": "chandler",
      "lastName": "bing",
      "exam": [
        1,
        2,
        3,
        5,
        6,
        7,
        8,
        9
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 1,
      "email": "Monica@abc",
      "password": "Geller",
      "type": "student",
      "firstName": "Monica",
      "lastName": "Geller",
      "exam": [
        1,
        2,
        3
      ],
      "taken": [
        0,
        0,
        1
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "email": "som@ad",
      "password": "1234",
      "type": "student",
      "firstName": "abhishek",
      "lastName": "sinha",
      "exam": [
        3,
        2,
        2
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "email": "a1@adobe.com",
      "password": "1234",
      "type": "student",
      "firstName": "anjn",
      "lastName": "nsa",
      "exam": [
        3,
        2,
        2
      ]
    },
    {
      "email": "2121",
      "password": "2121212",
      "type": "student",
      "firstName": "sa",
      "lastName": "12",
      "exam": [],
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "email": "dlkfjlsf",
      "password": "dfslkjfds",
      "type": "student",
      "firstName": "prinde",
      "lastName": "dkjfls",
      "exam": [],
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "email": "abh@adobe.com",
      "password": "1234",
      "type": "student",
      "firstName": "a1",
      "lastName": "b1",
      "exam": [],
      "id": 6
    }
  ],
  "exam": [
    {
      "examName": "Assignment 1",
      "id": 1,
      "startDate": 1500287205,
      "endDate": 1600493255,
      "duration": 6,
      "listOfQuestions": [
        0,
        1,
        2,
        8,
        4
      ]
    },
    {
      "examName": "Assignment 2",
      "startDate": 1500535560,
      "endDate": 1500539760,
      "duration": 70,
      "listOfQuestions": [],
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "examName": "Assignment 3",
      "startDate": 1500287205,
      "endDate": 1500287205,
      "duration": 4,
      "id": 3,
      "listOfQuestions": [
        0,
        1
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "examName": "eXAM1",
      "startDate": 1500287205,
      "endDate": 1600493255,
      "duration": 1,
      "listOfQuestions": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "examName": "exam_1",
      "startDate": 0,
      "endDate": 0,
      "duration": 0,
      "listOfQuestions": [
        3,
        4
      ],
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "examName": "exam_2",
      "startDate": 0,
      "endDate": 0,
      "duration": 0,
      "listOfQuestions": [
        5,
        6
      ],
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "examName": "exam_3",
      "startDate": 0,
      "endDate": 0,
      "duration": 0,
      "listOfQuestions": [
        7,
        8
      ],
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "examName": "exam_4",
      "startDate": 0,
      "endDate": 0,
      "duration": 0,
      "listOfQuestions": [
        9,
        10
      ],
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "examName": "exam_5",
      "startDate": 0,
      "endDate": 0,
      "duration": 0,
      "listOfQuestions": [
        11,
        12
      ],
      "id": 9
    }
  ],
  "question": [
    {
      "id": 0,
      "questionText": "demo",
      "marks": 1,
      "correctAnswer": "A",
      "listOfChoices": [
        "a",
        "b",
        "c",
        "d"
      ],
      "type": "Multi"
    },
    {
      "questionText": "hello worl",
      "marks": "4",
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "listOfChoices": [
        "opa",
        "opb",
        "opc"
      ],
      "type": "Multi",
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "questionText": "Hello World 2",
      "marks": "4",
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "listOfChoices": [
        "opa",
        "opb",
        "opc",
        "opd"
      ],
      "type": "Multi",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "questionText": "hello worl",
      "marks": "4",
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "listOfChoices": [
        "opa",
        "opb",
        "opc"
      ],
      "type": "Multi",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "questionText": "q2",
      "marks": "3",
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "listOfChoices": [
        "dhhdoq",
        "hdo",
        "hidq"
      ],
      "type": "Single",
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "questionText": "hello worl",
      "marks": "4",
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "listOfChoices": [
        "opa",
        "opb",
        "opc"
      ],
      "type": "Multi",
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "questionText": "q2",
      "marks": "3",
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "listOfChoices": [
        "dhhdoq",
        "hdo",
        "hidq"
      ],
      "type": "Single",
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "questionText": "hello worl",
      "marks": "4",
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "listOfChoices": [
        "opa",
        "opb",
        "opc"
      ],
      "type": "Multi",
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "questionText": "fill here __ name",
      "marks": "3",
      "correctAnswer": "alpha",
      "listOfChoices": [],
      "type": "Fill",
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "questionText": "hello worl",
      "marks": "4",
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "listOfChoices": [
        "opa",
        "opb",
        "opc"
      ],
      "type": "Multi",
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "questionText": "q2",
      "marks": "3",
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "listOfChoices": [
        "dhhdoq",
        "hdo",
        "hidq"
      ],
      "type": "Single",
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "questionText": "hello worl",
      "marks": "4",
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "listOfChoices": [
        "opa",
        "opb",
        "opc"
      ],
      "type": "Multi",
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "questionText": "q2",
      "marks": "3",
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "listOfChoices": [
        "dhhdoq",
        "hdo",
        "hidq"
      ],
      "type": "Single",
      "id": 12
    }
  ],
  "responses": [
    {
      "id": 0,
      "userId": 1,
      "questionId": 3,
      "responseText": "012"
    },
    {
      "userId": 1,
      "questionId": 0,
      "responseText": "",
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "userId": 1,
      "questionId": 1,
      "responseText": "",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "userId": 1,
      "questionId": 2,
      "responseText": "",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "userId": 1,
      "questionId": 8,
      "responseText": "sas",
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "userId": 1,
      "questionId": 4,
      "responseText": "",
      "id": 5
    }
  ]
}